# Marisa Vukas

As a Full-Stack Software Engineer with a passion for music production and playing the violin for over a decade, I bring a unique perspective to my work. My experience in music has developed my creativity and ability to think outside the box, which translates into innovative ideas and solutions in technology. Highly driven, self-motivated, and enjoys working in a team environment.

# **PROJECTS**

Poblano's Grill Web App — <a href="https://github.com/marisavukas/poblanos">https://github.com/marisavukas/poblanos</a>

Built with: React and Node.js.

- A fully responsive restaurant app made without a template to showcase my CSS abilities.
- Utilized useState React Hooks for food cart items and conditionally renders user input to show user selection.
- Implemented checkout page utilizing useEffect React Hook and stored cart items to local storage.

Website Portfolio App — <a href="https://github.com/marisavukas/react-bootstrap-portfolio">https://github.com/marisavukas/react-bootstrap-portfolio</a>

Built with: React, Bootstrap, and Node.js.

- Utilized useState React Hook, allowing collapsing navigation bar.
- Implemented a one-page app with responsive user interface and smooth navigation.

Online Metronome App — <a href="https://github.com/marisavukas/metronome">https://github.com/marisavukas/metronome</a>

Built with: React, Tone.js, and Node.js.

 Responsive app made from scratch using Tone.js library, allowing users to customize beats per minute and play/pause functionality for seamless user experience.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Edify Labs,** Fishers, IN — Workflow Developer

NOVEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Collaborated with the development team to design JSON configurations for cutting-edge custom modules within workflows, incorporating new and innovative technology.
- Acted as a technical resource within the team, providing collaborative support in resolving workflow-related challenges.
- Utilized ongoing creative and innovative ideas to leverage ChatGPT API, with the goal of continuously enhancing and streamlining customer service efficiency.

d2index, Westminster, CO — Software Engineer Intern

JULY 2022 - PRESENT

# https://d2index.com/

- Working on the front-end team, where my duties include designing and implementing UIs in React.js, resolving bugs, and participating in a product-driven agile process.
- Built reusable UI components using styled-components to increase scalability and reusability.
- Designed and implemented the News page UI, using a mobile first philosophy.
- Worked on a 3D NFT Gallery Prototype, which allows users to walk through a gallery of purchased NFTs with a first-person camera using React Three Fiber.
- Assembled cryptocurrency graphs on the Home page using Chart.js and REST APIs.

**Indiana** Emergency Care, Lafayette, IN — Medical Scribe

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2020

- $\bullet \ \ Documented \ and \ Proofread \ all \ aspects \ of \ a \ medical \ note \ in \ an \ emergency \ room \ setting.$
- · Worked alongside physicians and healthcare providers, to ensure accurate medical documentation.

# **EDUCATION**

Treehouse Code, Carmel, IN

**JANUARY 2022** 

Relevant Courses: HTML, CSS, Node and JavaScript.

**Marian University**, Indianapolis, IN — Pursued Master of Science in Biomedical Sciences

AUGUST 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN — Bachelor of Science, Nutrition Science

MAY 2020

#### CONTACT

marisavukas@gmail.com

## LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marisa-vukas/

## **Portfolio**

marisavukas.com

#### **SKILLS**

## Languages

- JavaScript
- · HTML
- · CSS
- Flexbox
- ∘ Grid
- TypeScript

## Frameworks

- React
- · React Native
- BootStrap
- Node.js
- · Three.js
- · Tone.js
- · Express.js
- Styled-components

## **TOOLS**

- PostgreSQL
- GitHub
- Heroku